Guide to the Percy Reese Morgan papers, 1900-1961.
Morgan, Percy Reese papers, 1900-1961.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Percy Reese Morgan papers, 1900-1961.
4449
Percy Reese Morgan.
2.5 cubic ft.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Papers of Percy Reese Morgan, a fruit farmer in Lewiston, N.Y. and observer for the U.S. Weather Bureau in the Lewiston area.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Fruit farmer in Lewiston, N.Y. and observer for the U.S. Weather Bureau in the Lewiston area. His wife was Mary Dodge Morgan.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence with family, friends, business associates and public officials; farm records; farm animal health and veterinary records; weather reports, 1949-1960; handwritten and typescript diaries, 1921-1961; extension reports; records of the Lewiston-Queenston Rotary Club; items relating to the New York State Horticultural Association; and pamphlets and brochures.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Morgan, Percy Reese.; Morgan, Mary Dodge.; Cornell University. Cooperative Extension.; Lewiston-Queenston Rotary Club.; New York State Horticultural Association.; United States. Weather Bureau.
Subjects:
Family--New York (State)--Lewiston.; Fruit-culture--New York (State)--Lewiston.; Animal health.; Farms--New York (State)--Niagara County.; Agriculture--Accounting.; Weather forecasting--New York (State)--Lewiston.; Rotary clubs--New York (State)--Lewiston.
Places:
Niagara County (N.Y.)--History, Local.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence, etc. "A". (1.), 1937-1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, Bills. "A". (2.), 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, Extension reports. "A"., 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, job orders, postcards. "A". (4.), 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, etc. "B". (1.), 1906, 1909, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, invoices. "B". (2.), 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, invoices. "B". (3.), 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, invoices, and other accounts. "B". (4.), 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, etc. "B". (5.), 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Conservation reports, Extension service reports, invoices. "C". (1.), 1938-1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Conservation reports, clippings, invoices. "C". (2.), 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Conservation reports, correspondence, Extension service reports, invoices. "C". (3.), 1954-1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, brochures, Bills. "D". (1.), 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, etc. "D". (2.), 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Correspondence. "D". (3.), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Correspondence. "D". (4.), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Correspondence. "D". (5.), 1960 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Extension service reports, correspondence. "E"., 1941-1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, clippings, etc. "F". (1.), 1905, 1948-1954 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Correspondence. "F". (2.), 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Correspondence. "F". (3.), 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, etc. "G"., 1942-1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, bills. "H". (1.), 1905, 1943, 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, bills, and other invoices. "H". (2.), 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, bills, and other invoices. "H". (3.), 1957 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Correspondence. "H". (4.), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Correspondence. "H". (5.), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Correspondence. "H". (6.), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Correspondence. "H". (7.), 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Income Tax and insurance statements. "I"., 1949-1960 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, bills. "J"., 1949-1959 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, bills, invoices. "K". (1.), 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, invoices. "K". (2.), 1957 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, invoices, bills. "K". (3.), 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, invoices, labor income. "L". (1.), 1949-1952 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, etc. "L". (2.), 1953-1960 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, invoices and orders. "M". (1.), 1900, 1905, 1918, 1944-1950 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Correspondence, bills and invoices. "M". (3.), 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Postcards, correspondence. "M". (4.), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Correspondence. "M". (5.), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Correspondence. "M". (6.), 1960 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Correspondence, map, invoices. "N". (1.), 1905-1906, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, bills and invoices. "N". (2.), 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bills and invoices. "N". (3.), 1953 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, invoices. "N". (4.), 1954 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, invoices. "N". (5.), 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, bills. "O"., 1950-1958 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, a play written by PRW, memorials for Mary Dodge Morgen, invoices. "P"., 1949-1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Rotary club correspondence, invoices, other correspondence. "R". (1.), 1935-1951 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Rotary club correspondence, invoices, other correspondence. "R". (2.), 1952-1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, etc. "S". (1.), 1905, 1934, 1948-1950 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, invoices and bills. "S". (2.), 1951-1954 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, invoices and bills. "S". (3.), 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Tax statements, correspondence, etc. "T". (1.), 1907, 1935, 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Tax statements, correspondence, etc. "T". (2.), 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, bills. "U"., 1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Animal health reports, bills and invoices. "V"., 1948-1960 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Estate Appraisal of Felix Woolworth done by PRM, wheat allotment reports, correspondence, bills. "W". (1.), 1939-1955 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, bills., 1956-1961 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, bills., 1949-1960 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Clipping re: zoning applications., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Artificial Breeding Association Receipts., 1943-1957 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Beekeeping., 1942-1952 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Bulletins, pamphlets, newsletters., 1937-1955 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Extension Service Information sheets., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Extension Service Information sheets., 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Extension Service Programs and Information sheets., 1942-1954 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Dairy Farm Service Letters., 1938-1943 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Erie County Savings Bank book. (Buffalo, N.Y.), 1887-1905 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Morgan family history., n.d. (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Farm Service Letters and Miscellaneous., 1940-1950 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Lewiston Meat Market and Frozen Food Locker Service., 1948-1959 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous - Fruit, Bulbs, other information sheets., 1937-1957 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- New York Telephone Company Service statements., 1940-1960 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Niagara County Historical Society and local history., 1939, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation Electric bills., 1940-1960 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Obituaries (Mary Dodge Morgan and Percy Reese Morgan)., 1957-1961 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Purchase orders and invoices., 1943-1952 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Tax Forms for fuel and other farm equipment., 1938-1957 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- United States Department of Commerce Weather Bureau Certificate of Authority., Sept. 21, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Veterinary records., 1941-1954 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Water Department Bills, Town of Lewiston, New York., 1950-1960 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Weather Reports, Correspondence and newspaper clippings., 1949-1960 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Correspondence with Richard Templeton including court documents re: last will and testament of Hiram Dodge., 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Personal typescript diary of Percy Reese Morgan. (PRM), 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Personal cash accounts., 1958 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Personal typescript diary of PRM., 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Personal handwritten diary of PRM., ca. 1923-1924 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Personal handwritten diary of PRM., 1930 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Personal handwritten diary of PRM., 1921 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Personal handwritten diary of PRM., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Personal handwritten diary of PRM., 1923 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Personal handwritten diary of PRM., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Bound typescript diary of Percy Reese Morgan. (PRM), Jan. 1948-Jan. 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Photographic negatives (Box 5)
- Typescript diary of PRM., Jan. 1952-Dec. 1954 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Typescript diary of PRM., Jan. 1955-Jan. 1958 (Box 6, Folder 2)